[heartbeat whooshing through machine]
[whooshing continues]
[phone buzzes]
[heartbeat continues]
All right, we're done.
[machine beeps]
Is everything okay?
Make an appointment with your cardiologist
as soon as possible.
[ominous music playing]
[door closes]
[dramatic music playing]
[Teagan] Mom, the shower's broken.
I know, I'm working on it.
It's just, we have to move
from well water to the town plumbing,
and this is a heritage house,
so we need a permit.
-Mine just got rejected.
-How long is that gonna take?
-I have to shower.
-Use my deodorant spray.
-It'll buy you a day or two.
-Mom.
-That can't be the solution.
-There's a board of appeals.
Oh! I have an in with the state senator,
DeeDee Garner.
-We used to do the pageant circuit.
-That's Baloo and Britney's mom.
Are you friends?
Friends with one of them,
the other wants me dead.
What about you with DeeDee?
Oh, wants me dead too.
But I mean, it's been so long,
it's probably fine.
And if not, I will carve out a budget
for dry shampoo.
[Teagan] Teagan says pull.
Teagan says freeze.
-Where's Josh? Why isn't he here?
-I dunno, I haven't heard from him.
So practice is optional now.
Row.
-Teagan says.
-Crap.
Teagan says pull.
Okay.
Teagan says, rate up for a beat.
Teagan says, give me a "Yes, ma'am!"
[all] Yes, ma'am!
[Teagan] Okay.
Coming for stroke.
You give it your best shot.
You might be the fastest,
but it'll never happen.
Don't be so sure about that.
No one's gonna follow a faid over a Regis.
[somber music playing]
[Teagan] Cam.
I have been promised tacos,
and I've come to collect.
[both laugh quietly]
Is everything okay?
Get ready for some tacos
that will change your life.
[laughing] Oh, wow,
I'm from SoCal. I highly doubt that.
[Baloo] What's this?
[intriguing music playing]
[singsong] Oh, Ryder!
Got a box for you.
"You have stolen my heart."
"Will you go to the Fall Formal with me?
From Amber."
[Baloo] Aw.
Hold on, so she's giving you a heart
and then saying you stole it?
Which is it?
And why does it look like a ransom note?
Can you guys not ruin the magic
of this promposal right now?
Wait, is it really a promposal
if it's for the Fall Formal?
-Is it more like a form-posal?
-That's not better.
Well, it looks like
I got a date to the Fall Formal.
I'll organize the table for the dance.
Who's coming?
Baloo, you bringing Thirst Trap Guy?
Uh…
Didn't pan out. Just me this year.
Showing up at the end of practice,
that's a choice.
Dentist appointment.
Cleared it with Coach.
Getting my workout in now.
Glad we could work around your schedule.
[boy clearing throat]
[school bell ringing]
[indistinct chatter]
I'll catch up with you outside.
Okay.
Time to talk.
Okay, let's talk.
Wanna explain your sudden pivot
from being just friends?
-I thought that part was pretty clear.
-I thought we were gonna let this go.
-What if I didn't want to?
-What if you made yourself do it anyway?
I don't know
that I'm supposed to be with Britney.
Come on, Josh,
you guys are perfect for each other.
You're both the worst people that I know.
Yeah, I don't think she'd like me
if I wasn't… this.
What's going on with you?
I, uh…
Uh…
It's nothing. I-it's fine.
Whatever's happening in your life,
I'm not going to be the excuse
to run away from it.
You have to deal with it.
Hey, you have so much, Josh.
So just…
before you throw everything away,
take a look at what you'd be losing.
Hey, you're Madison, right?
-Is your dad around?
-Yeah, he's just prepping for the dance.
Can I help you?
Teagan forgot her homework assignment,
and I thought I'd drop it off.
-You could just leave it with me.
-I don't mind waiting.
Let me save you some time.
I've seen this before.
The drop by, the smile, the coffee.
You're not the first PTA mom to come by.
But it never happens. He's not looking.
No, that's not what this is.
I'm just… Your dad and I are old friends.
Sure.
You know what?
I'll leave this here.
-Hey! Hi.
-Ella, hey. What are you doing here?
I had to drop off Teagan's homework,
and I thought I'd give you one of these.
From Discovery, my favorite spot.
[Ella] Oat milk latte, extra shot.
Thank you. I could really use this.
FYI, he prefers decaf after 9.
I gotta move this gear.
[Hayden laughs quietly]
It was nice to meet you.
[Madison] Mm-hmm.
Love you.
Yeah.
-Well, Madison seems a little…
-Intense. It's her default mode.
-Okay.
-Always running interference.
She's more bark than bite though,
I promise you.
So what are you up to Saturday night?
Dinner?
I have to work at the Crab Shack.
How about Friday?
Can't do Friday.
I am chaperoning the formal.
Actually, we could use some help.
No, you lost me at chaperone.
What, trying to police
100 hormonal teenagers not fun?
What about hanging with other chaperones,
including your personal favorite,
DeeDee Garner?
Uh-huh.
Uh, you know what? Sign me up.
I didn't know you two kept in touch.
We didn't, but it's time for a reunion.
[knocking]
Hey, coach duty calls.
See you at the dance.
Ryder Regis, come on in.
What's on your mind?
Big news, actually.
I had a video chat with the coach
from the Dartmouth rowing program,
and he invited me
to the campus next Tuesday.
-It's cool if I miss practice, right?
-No, I need my stroke seat there.
You'll have to find another day to go.
You let Josh miss a day,
but I can't do what I have to do?
Josh had a dental issue.
-It's preferential treatment.
-It really isn't.
It's my team, so my call.
[pensive music playing]
Wow.
Hi, babe.
I have a surprise for you.
I can see that.
It's a recreation of our first date.
When you took me
to that perfect chalet in Rhône Valley.
I had our faves flown in.
Macarons from La Bissette,
éclairs from La Lyonnaise.
-And the opera cake from--
-From Sabine's.
[giggles] I knew you'd remember.
But why the trip down memory lane?
You're promposing to me, silly.
I know you've had a lot going on
with your family and Ryder.
So I thought I'd plan it for you,
especially since there's a photo shoot.
Over here, thank you.
-Oh, uh…
-[Britney laughs]
Your grandfather always loved
Bespoke Magazine.
Well, they're featuring us in a spread.
-[camera clicking]
-How did you swing that?
I pitched them an article
about a next-gen power couple,
which will build my public profile.
[Josh] This is amazing.
The article starts
with how we were voted
King and Queen of the Fall Formal.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm.
Congrats, babe.
To us. We are a great team.
I provide the publicity,
the political power,
you the pedigree and charisma,
not to mention the abs.
-[both laugh]
-[uneasy music playing]
Come here.
[camera clicking]
-[Teagan] Oh!
-[Cam] It's got a kick. So?
-Solid B plus.
-B plus?
It's a great grade. Way above average
for East Coast Mexican food.
-I'm offended.
-I'm from LA.
-I have loyalties.
-Okay.
[Teagan] Ow!
Are you okay?
Yeah, I just… I hit a blister
from my last erg session.
-Oh yeah, that's a beaut.
-[Teagan laughs]
-I popped a good one yesterday right here.
-[Teagan] Oh!
That one is not messing around.
I know you're supposed to leave them
alone because of infection, but…
I can't row with it.
I keep meaning to deal with mine,
but I can't with my left hand.
-I can take care of it if you want.
-Really?
It doesn't bother me
if it doesn't bother you.
Come on, I got a first aid kit inside.
Okay.
Not quite how I expected
this date to go down, but…
Yup.
[soft music playing]
Ready?
Okay.
So attractive.
[both laughing]
It's the life of a rower.
My mom always asks me
why I'm obsessed with crew,
but I never know how to explain it.
It's not an obsession. It's just…
who I am.
Same.
It's where I feel the most… like me.
Okay, I know this sounds crazy,
but when I watch the Olympics,
I keep thinking…
I can do that. You know,
that's where I'm supposed to be.
Even if I'm just
some guy from Eagle's Cove.
I just need people to believe in me.
They do.
Not really.
No one sees me in stroke.
If I can't win them over,
I don't stand a chance.
How do you do it?
You got them to listen.
I mean, you even got a "Yes, ma'am."
-You want a "Yes, ma'am"?
-Yeah, who doesn't want a "Yes, ma'am"?
But seriously… What am I doing wrong?
Maybe...
they don't follow you because
they don't know who you really are.
You always have your guard up,
you're kind of… a mystery.
Right.
You need to let them in.
Hang out with them, you know.
Show them the Cam that I know.
How?
Maybe we should go
to Fall Formal with them.
Is this a promposal?
You couldn't tell by the romantic tacos
with a side of blisters?
It's perfect.
[Teagan giggles]
I don't know where I'm gonna find a suit.
Well, we do know a guy.
[catwalk music playing]
So what are we feeling?
Pedro Pascal Met Gala,
Paul Mescal swag, Bad Bunny big swing?
What's the vibe? Right? What's resonating?
-Nope. Mistakes made. I'm out.
-Whoa. Okay, hang on, look.
You need to get out of your comfort zone.
Perry, dial it back a bit.
Sorry. I'm just really excited
to get rid of those chinos.
Okay, okay.
Look, a suit makes a man.
Why don't you tell me
a bit about your style?
Does it fit, and is it clean?
Hm.
Comfortable. Not showy, but… proud.
Hang on.
[whispering] Chu-chu-chu…
Ah!
-Here you are.
-[Teagan] Hm!
Wait, how did you do that?
Call it a gift. Suit up.
[upbeat music playing]
The designer sent some outfits for you
over with my dress so we match properly.
I think you should wear this one.
-Oh. Uh… Cool.
-Mm!
As king and queen,
we get a head table
so we can invite the crew
to be our royal court
with photos with them
scheduled before the dance.
Ah, those guys are so photogenic.
Then it's dinner, dancing, more photos,
then finally
the king and queen slow dance.
Wow, it sounds like you have
the whole day planned out.
Well, yeah, babe, it's a big deal.
Hey, do you think
we could hang before the dance?
I just thought we could talk.
There's just some things on my mind that…
If we do that, I won't have time
for my hair appointment.
And you know Alejandro
he hates being rushed.
I know.
Maybe we can later.
-[knocking on door]
-Ooh.
That might be the jeweler.
-Hi.
-Mom.
I thought we were going
to meet up at the dance.
Oh, my Fall Formal Queen.
[gasps] And her king.
Lovely to see you, Senator Garner.
Did you get in okay from Beacon Hill?
I got out early,
so I thought maybe we could
squeeze in dinner and a mani-pedi.
Sorry, Mom,
we're running on a tight schedule.
I'll see you tomorrow?
Uh…
-All right, darling.
-Yeah. Okay.
-Bye.
-[Josh] Take care.
[Britney] Oh, we gotta take this in.
[man] Yeah, I saw the deadline
on the notice.
Look, I know we're a few months late.
It's a slow season.
I just need a couple extra weeks.
Okay, good. Thank you.
-Dad, everything okay?
-Nothing to worry about.
But your new school uniform
is gonna have to wait.
You okay with the old one?
Yeah, it's fine.
And can you pitch in
on the evening shifts this week?
-Yeah, of course.
-Great.
Except for Friday.
I'm taking someone to Fall Formal.
-Well, fantastic.
-Yeah, but, I mean, I could stay.
No, no, absolutely not.
Who's the lucky date?
Her name's Teagan. She's on crew.
A girl after your own heart.
Could I take the truck then?
No. You can't take a girl
to a dance in that.
I've got a client
who owes me a bit of a favor.
You're gonna go in style.
Come on. Check this out.
["My Everything" by W.E.T. playing]
♪ Don't wanna let you down ♪
♪ And I don't get excited ♪
♪ Even for a minute that's too far ♪
♪ You're my everything
Bigger than the stars ♪
♪ What a thing to be where you are ♪
♪ And you made me see
From the very start ♪
♪ Nowhere I'd rather be
Than in your arms ♪
♪ The love we share will let you know ♪
Is Coach Hayden in?
He just stepped out to the boatsheds.
Ah.
Hey, do you have a moment?
I actually have a coach problem
that I was hoping you could solve.
Ow-ah!
-Okay, careful, Mom.
-Stop squirming.
Hurry, I'm getting picked up any minute.
We wouldn't be rushing
if you hadn't gone rowing.
He's a rower?
Yeah.
-You met Cam at the regatta.
-Oh.
Right. Yeah, he seems very nice.
You don't remember him, do you?
Of course I do.
He was the one wearing the hat.
-Yeah, they were all in hats, Mom.
-[laughing]
All right, we're done here.
[giggles]
Time for the big reveal.
Oh.
-Oh?
-You look beautiful.
Thanks, Mom.
[vehicle approaching]
Okay. He's here.
-Goodness. Look at this.
-Okay.
Hello, shoulders. Is your date Superman?
Mom, stop!
Okay.
Wow, Teagan.
Hi.
-Ready to go?
-Yeah.
Yeah. Are you guys
still good to give me a lift?
Just kidding.
She's not kidding. Okay, go!
-Bye.
-Go, go, go!
[laughing] Bye.
And you can take over the coat check,
and you can keep the feisty ones
out of the rose garden.
Hi, sorry I'm late. I'm Teagan's mama.
DeeDee Garner, is that you?
-Ella Emerson, you're back in the cove.
-Yeah.
And still on your own personal schedule.
Well, I'm here to help now.
-Let's find something for you to do.
-So what have you been up to?
-It's been 20 years.
-Harvard, Yale for law.
I'm a state senator now. How about you?
Well, I got married
and then that ended, so…
And that's what brought you back home.
Yes, I've taken over my parents' place,
which has been a maintenance nightmare.
But I think you know a thing or two
about heritage houses.
I see you've been doing some research.
I recently applied for a permit
to fix my plumbing,
but it was denied
by the heritage committee,
so I thought maybe there might be a way
for you to put a good word in for me.
[laughs]
I don't think so.
Ah. Here we go.
Looks like the punch table
could use some cups.
You think you can handle cups?
Sure, it's just cups.
Friggin' cups.
Hey, you guys. Since when do you DJ?
He's not DJ-ing tonight, I am.
Unless you want a two-hour set
of Nelly and Destiny's Child.
-Hey, play nice.
-I can't wait to dance to your set.
Your participation is not necessary.
[Hayden] Maddy.
Sorry about that.
I'm gonna go try to find DeeDee
and see where I'm stationed.
-See you.
So, I looked you up online.
Okay, cool. Well, I have nothing to hide.
This is true, there's not much there.
No school, no employment history, just…
wife of a felon.
And assistant manager
at the Crab Shack, probationary.
Right, so I just wanna know,
if you are pursuing my father,
what do you bring to the table?
[upbeat music playing]
[photographer] Okay, if I can have you
both just staring into each other's eyes.
Fantastic, Britney.
Looking very presidential. Perfect.
Next, just the queen and her mother.
-Looking dapper.
-You too, man.
The royal court has arrived.
Oh!
King of fashion over here.
-[Josh] Pink-hair Perry!
-Boys.
Come on, bro.
Regis.
-Dude, what is good, man?
-Good to see you, bro.
[Amber] Hi, boys.
-[Josh] You look beautiful.
-[Ryder] What happened to tie a tie?
[Crabcatcher] Baloo, you clean up nice.
-Crabby.
-[Noah] That's some suit, Baloo.
What's up, man? Looking good.
-[Perry] Hey, where's Cam?
-[Crabcatcher] Lookin' good.
[Perry] Everyone's so fresh.
["Poquito mas" by Kacy Hill playing]
[Josh] Whoa.
[Noah] Who's this?
[all exclaiming]
[Baloo] Come on! You look good.
I did that. That was me. I'm a genius.
Thanks, guys.
Hey, who's the lucky date?
♪ Like seeing the signs
Now that it's over ♪
♪ One, two at a time
Pushing me closer ♪
Yes!
♪ Time never lasts
Just like they told you ♪
♪ Seeing the signs now that it's over ♪
♪ Sometimes ♪
♪ I still care ♪
Get out there. Come on.
Bring it in.
Hey, guys, we need photos of the court.
Let's head inside.
-All right.
-Let's go.
-This is it.
-Okay.
-[Britney] You look nice.
-[Perry] Thanks.
-Come on.
-Yeah.
[Hayden] Welcome, everyone. Come on in.
Please find your table, take your seats.
[boy] Come over here, sit with me.
[Britney] Okay. Can you hold this? Thanks.
Here we go.
Wow. And there we are.
And the lapel.
Josh and Britney,
it's time for the king and queen entrance.
[both screaming]
[Britney] Okay, okay. Hi.
So, you and Cam. Looks official.
If you can't say something nice,
shut the hell up.
Okay, fair.
You look great. Both of you.
-[Hayden] Please welcome the royal court.
-Thank you.
[Hayden] The senior boys' rowing team.
[dramatic, upbeat music playing]
-Please be seated for the entrance.
-Josh! We have to go.
-Okay.
-Come.
-All right!
-[student] Britney, I love you!
And now, put your hands together
for your Fall Formal King and Queen,
Britney Garner and Josh Regis.
[upbeat music continues]
Whoo!
♪ It doesn't matter ♪
♪ I can't stop
It doesn't matter ♪
♪ We're gon' fly
♪ It doesn't matter ♪
[sighs] Thank you.
[song ends]
So, this orange thing is
"a compressed melon with micro basil."
-How badly do you want a burger right now?
-[laughs]
Cam Dillinger. Are you having fun?
You caught me.
[laughs]
[Teagan and Cam laughing]
Hey. The boys and I are going
for a donut run if you want in.
I think it might be fun.
There's no way
powdered sugar is going near this dress.
And we are king and queen.
We cannot just leave.
No one's gonna care
if we're gone for 20 minutes.
I care.
I don't wanna miss any part of our night.
Do you think we'll ever be
the most popular ones at Easton?
I think that with you
at the head of the dance committee
and me in stroke seat
that… we can do anything.
And now for a little something
to start the festivities.
["Cursed Romantics"
by Maude Latour playing]
Oh!
-This is my jam.
-Let's boogie.
-[Baloo] Come on, buddy. Let's go.
-Let's go.
♪ Baby, we're just cursed romantics ♪
Come on. The dance floor is calling us.
-Come on. Let's go.
-Yeah.
♪ Oh damn, I hate this part
Violet delights have violent ends ♪
♪ What do I do
When your love has changed me? ♪
♪ It's so impressive
When you overtake me ♪
♪ Your love is poison and nobody can… ♪
I know a way
you can really get the team behind you.
-Yeah, what's that?
-Mm-hmm.
-Show us your moves.
-Not happening.
The whole team's out there.
Come on.
[Teagan giggles]
It's fun.
All right.
♪ We're just cursed romantics ♪
♪ Tragedy, catastrophe ♪
♪ Beautiful, so dramatic ♪
-[dance music playing]
-[people whooping and cheering]
♪ Let's make some arrangements ♪
♪ Can I make your acquaintance?
That next-level dimension ♪
♪ That's why I'm not to mention
Is that beyond your comprehension? ♪
♪ Are you gonna come to the after party
To the after party, to the after party? ♪
♪ Are you gonna come
'Cause I like to party ♪
♪ 'Cause I like to party
♪ To the after party
The after party, the after party ♪
♪ 'Cause I like to party
'Cause I like to party ♪
♪ You've got me so high
That I can't leave ♪
[different song playing]
[all chanting] Go, Crabby! Go, Crabby!
Go, Crabby! Go, Crabby! Go, Crabby!
[cheering]
Go, Baloo! Go, Baloo!
Work it, Baloo!
[encouraging and cheering]
Oh!
-That's my cue to go get some punch.
-Whoa, nice try, Dillinger.
It's almost your turn.
No, no, I'm not going in there.
I'm terrible.
Can't be worse
than Bert and Ernie over here.
Quaid, put me down!
Go, Perry! Let's go, Perry!
Yeah, I'm not following that.
Do you want to be stroke or not?
Go!
[Teagan] Whoo!
-[boy] Yo, dance!
-[Teagan] Hey! Look at me.
[all exclaiming and cheering]
Whoa, Cam!
[Quaid] Whoa, Cam!
Did you know he could do that?
-Hey, is everything okay?
-The air-conditioning shut off.
We need to get it back on
before this room turns into a swamp.
Okay, well, I could maybe call someone.
I'm sure you maybe could.
Why are you so mad?
What did I do?
It's not important.
Bet we tripped the breaker the AC is on.
Ugh.
Ah.
And we have cool air.
Just like that?
What?
Did you shut the door?
-Uh…
-[doorknob rattling]
We're trapped.
God, I am in town for exactly 48 hours
to see my daughter's special moment.
Now I'm going to miss it because of you.
I'm really sorry, DeeDee.
It was an accident.
It's never your fault, is it?
Why do you have it in for me?
Do you want to know what you did?
You're helpless.
Even back in our pageant days,
you always needed to bum a ride,
or you'd forget your hairspray,
or need help with your dress.
You were helpless, and you relied
on everyone else to put you together.
You asked me, a state senator, for help
with a local permit. It's pathetic.
Okay.
You've said your piece.
What are you doing?
Getting us out of here.
-Do you know what you're doing?
-Of course not.
[lively music playing]
Oh look, it's me if I had no taste.
Oh look, it's me with no finesse.
Walking away.
-Mm!
-Tell her to change now.
Who?
Juliet. She's wearing my look.
You're both making it work.
I'm making it work better.
You know, Perry,
you've been clocking her all night
and for a while now.
[scoffs]
-Excuse me?
-Okay, come on.
Has it ever occurred to you
that maybe you have a thing for her?
Impossible. We fight all the time.
She's the Dior to my Coco Chanel.
So maybe you finally met your match.
What? No.
You two kind of get each other
in a way that no one else does.
That is… curious.
Just go ask her to dance.
You know you want to. Go on.
Last chance to get tickets
to the after-party.
It's a charity cruise for the EPFA.
Up for a romantic moonlit trip
through the Harbor Islands?
Tickets are 250 each. Who's in?
Yeah, put me down for two.
I got a hot date.
-Anyone else? Noah, Cam?
-Sure.
-Oh, um…
-I don't wanna go.
We're having a good time.
-I'm not dressed for the cold.
-[Perry] You should go.
I'll take three.
-Hey, come on. That's like 750 bucks.
-Don't worry about it.
It's going to a good cause.
Thanks, Perry.
Let's go talk to them.
See? You're making progress.
Even Perry's got your back.
Do you know what the EPFA is?
Should I?
It's the Easton Prep
Financial Aid program.
The one that goes to my tuition.
I'm the good cause.
Oh.
Hey. Are you okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
You actually made it back.
Huh!
I apologize for getting short with you.
It's fine.
Actually, DeeDee, it's not fine.
I know you think I'm flaky or whatever,
but now I'm a single mother
to a teenage girl.
For the last eight months,
I've had to be everything to her.
And when something
needs to get done for her, I get it done.
It doesn't matter how many vents
I need to crawl through
or how many state senators I need to beg.
Duly noted.
Okay, great. Well, can you help me
get this permit approved, please?
I'll see what I can do.
You know, I spend most of the year
in Beacon Hill.
When I come home,
my daughter acts like I'm invisible.
It's like she hates me.
Oh, well, my two cents,
if it makes you feel any better,
she doesn't hate you. It's just…
just how teenage girls are.
You think so?
Yeah, I'm stuck with mine all the time,
and it's the same.
[both laughing]
But once in a blue moon,
they need their moms.
And you know what? You'll be there.
[upbeat music playing]
You really like this one, don't you?
What gave it away?
Your face. You forgot to be subtle.
She seems okay.
She is. A little more than okay.
Listen, thanks for running defense
since your mom died.
I know you've been looking out for me.
Can you let this one through?
I'll holster the glare.
-Thank you. Okay. [laughing]
-For now.
We could hit the dance floor.
Or we can… just sit.
Yeah.
Cam, it's not a big deal.
Yeah. Not to you.
[emotional music playing]
Look, you said I need to show them
who I am so they'll want to follow me.
-Yeah.
-What am I supposed to show them?
Hey, that I can't afford a new uniform?
That I have to work shifts
at the shop after school?
And their after-party
pays for my education.
Is there anything in that
that someone wants to follow?
Okay, they don't want to see that, Teagan.
No one does.
-I do.
-Okay, but I don't want you to.
Like, no matter what I do,
no matter how hard I row
or how much I study
or how many shifts I work,
I'm just always so far away
from being who I wanna be.
-It's okay.
-No, it's not.
Look, I don't think
I can do this right now.
I'm sorry, Teagan.
[Britney exclaiming]
Look at the smolder on you.
We are announcing
the king and queen dance in a few minutes.
-Thank you.
-Okay, the last event of the night.
What's the matter with you?
It's like you don't even wanna be here.
I do.
I just…
When was the last time we actually talked?
Or just had fun together?
I am having fun. Aren't you?
No.
Not really.
I think we've been acting happy
more than we've been happy
for a really long time.
-Stop.
-Brit.
Don't tell me you can't see it.
We don't want the same things.
-And I'm not who you think I am.
-No.
No.
You are breaking up with me?
Here?
Now?
I can't pretend anymore.
I'm sorry.
Is it Teagan?
No.
It's just that… this is over.
[Hayden] And now it's time
for your king and queen
-to lead with their first dance.
-[students cheering]
[laughing]
Awesome.
Isn't that the perfect ending
to the article?
"Alone and ditched on the dance floor."
Thanks.
-[music playing]
-[Hayden] Put your hands together
for this year's reigning King and Queen
of the Fall Formal.
-[clapping and cheering]
-["Slow Burn" By Anna Leanne playing]
Hey. It doesn't have to end like that.
Can I take you out for one last dance?
♪ I try to be the one you want
But, baby, I'm just scared ♪
Josh Regis and Britney Garner.
♪ 'Cause suddenly all the summers
Turn with you into lifetimes lately ♪
♪ It feels like you are on fire
While it feels like a slow burn to me ♪
♪ Guess that I'm not ready
Maybe I'm just scared ♪
♪ I just need a little more time ♪
♪ Am I falling ♪
♪ Or making the same decision
That kept me from loving ♪
♪ But it just led to nothing ♪
♪ You're falling
I'm hating ♪
♪ The way that I just
Always keep you waiting ♪
♪ What if it's just… ♪
Look, if Cam can't get over himself,
that's his own problem.
I just don't know what I did.
Nothing.
If he doesn't feel
like he's enough for you,
there's nothing you can do.
Only he can change that.
Yeah.
Want to bail? Watch Saw in my room?
It'll be more romantic than this.
Juliet, I have something to tell you.
Your outfit.
You wore it best.
Would you like to dance?
Yes. Go on. Come on.
Go.
I will kill you.
You're welcome.
♪ What if it's just
Another lesson learned ♪
♪ What if love is not a slow burn ♪
["Blonde" by Sunday (1994) playing]
♪ I was supposed to be the one… ♪
[DeeDee] Britney.
I got you.
♪ My car won't start ♪
♪ And I feel so old in this parking lot ♪
Ryder.
Cabrera asked me to excuse you
from practice to meet with Dartmouth.
I came to you first.
You left me no choice.
So instead of prioritizing the team,
you decided to go over my head.
Cabrera already said I could go.
Which makes me think
you're not a serious leader.
-It's her call.
-Here's mine.
You are out of the stroke seat.
Effective immediately.
-But Coach--
-At the next regatta, we're starting Josh.
♪ I wanna be like her ♪
♪ I wanna dye my hair… ♪
[Josh] Hey.
What are you doing here?
Um… [laughs]
My night turned out to be a bust.
-Is everything okay?
-Yeah. Uh…
Turns out that Cam's not sure
he can do this right now.
Oh.
I'm sorry to hear that.
What are you doing here?
Uh, my night was also a bust.
I broke up with Britney.
Is that the right move?
It was.
Does that mean
she hates someone more than me now?
[laughs]
I think you're off the hook.
Now I am the most hated person
on both of your lists.
-[laughing]
-["Honeycrash" by Sasami playing]
I don't hate you.
♪ Think about all the nights
You used to hold me ♪
♪ Wonder why we couldn't make it out ♪
♪ And who can love you ♪
♪ Like I do right now ♪
♪ Honey, don't count me out ♪
♪ Even when the heavens sour ♪
♪ Even in your darkest hour ♪
♪ Even when the heart is cracked ♪
♪ Honey, crash into me ♪
♪ Like a storm into the sea ♪
♪ Like blood on the silver screen ♪
♪ We can make it through all that ♪
♪ Looking for someone
To help me forget it ♪
♪ Even though I know I'll regret it ♪
♪ Hoping you change your mind ♪
♪ And who can love you ♪
♪ Like I do right now ♪
♪ And if you leave ♪
♪ It better be ♪
♪ 'Cause you found someone
Who can love you better than me ♪
♪ Honey, don't count me out ♪
♪ Even when the heavens sour ♪
♪ Even in your darkest hour ♪
[song ends]